[
    {
        "question": "Which country is Ankara its capital?",
        "answer": "Turkey"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country is Seoul its capital?",
        "answer": "South Korea"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country is Mexico City its capital?",
        "answer": "Mexico"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country is Bras\u00edlia its capital?",
        "answer": "Brazil"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country is New Delhi its capital?",
        "answer": "India"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country is Buenos Aires its capital?",
        "answer": "Argentina"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country is Pretoria its capital?",
        "answer": "South Africa"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country is Tokyo its capital?",
        "answer": "Japan"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country is Cairo its capital?",
        "answer": "Egypt"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country is Riyadh its capital?",
        "answer": "Saudi Arabia"
    }
]